Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repair, Saugatuck, Proposal,1996 (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repair, Saugatuck,1996 (Box 338, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repair, Saugatuck, Blue-lines,1996 (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - NLB Fixed Yacht Docks, Petoskey,1996 (Box 338, Folder 9)
  - NLB Quarry Lake/ Harbor Lake, Petoskey,1996 (Box 338, Folder 10)
  - NLB Water Intake, Mosel, WI, Kohler Co,1996 (Box 338, Folder 11)
  - NLB Navigation Lights, Maumee Bay, OH,1996 (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - NLB Boat Launch Dredging, Pinconning Park, Bay County,1996 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - NLB Bridge Scour Protection, Ypsilanti,1996 (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dredging, Holland, Proposal,1996 (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dredging, Holland,1996 (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dredging, Holland, Blue-lines,1996 (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Dam Removal, Manistee,1996 (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Dam Removal, Manistee, Drawings,1996 (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - NLB Breakwater, Avon Lake, OH,1996 (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - NLB Bridge Scour Protection, Ypsilanti,1996 (Box 340, Folder 4)
  - NLB Floating Docks, City of Chicago, Park District, IL,1996 (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - NLB Floating Docks, City of Chicago, Park District, IL,1996 (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dredging, Erie, PA,1996 (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - NLB Consumer Power, Barrier Net, Ludington,1996 (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - NLB Manistique River and Harbor Sediment Capping, Manistique,1996 (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - NLB Manistique River and Harbor Sediment Capping, Manistique, Blue-lines, Photographs,1996 (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - NLB Environmental Remediation, Manistique,1996 (Box 341, Folder 3)
  - NLB Environmental Remediation, Manistique, Blue-lines,1996 (Box 341, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, Silver Bay, MN,1997 (Box 341, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, White Lake Harbor Repairs,1997 (Box 341, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, White Lake Harbor Repairs, Blue-lines,1997 (Box 341, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repairs, Milwaukee, WI,1997 (Box 342, Folder 1)
  - NLB Sault Ste. Marie Marina, Sault Ste. Marie,1997 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - NLB Sault Ste. Marie Marina, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines,1997 (Box 342, Folder 3)
  - NLB Sault Ste. Marie Marina, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines, Photographs,1997 (Box 342, Folder 4)
  - NLB Work Boat Harbor, Burns Harbor, IN,1997 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - NLB Pinconning Park Boat Launch Dredging, Bay County,1997 (Box 342, Folder 6)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Fish Barrier, Essexville,1997 (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - NLB Dredging, Tonawanda, NY,1997 (Box 343, Folder 2)
  - NLB Port Washington Harbor Improvements, Port Washington, WI,1997 (Box 343, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Navigation Light, Neebish Island,1997 (Box 343, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Navigation Light, Neebish Island, Drawings,1997 (Box 343, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dam Machinery Renovation, Fox River, WI,1997 (Box 343, Folder 6)
  - NLB Beaver Island Ferry Dock, Beaver Island,1997 (Box 343, Folder 7)
  - NLB Beaver Island Ferry Dock, Beaver Island, Blue-lines, 1 of 2,1997 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - NLB Beaver Island Ferry Dock, Beaver Island, Blue-lines, 2 of 2,1997 (Box 344, Folder 2)
  - NLB North Point Marina Erosion Protection, North Point, IL,1997 (Box 344, Folder 3)
  - NLB Breakwater and SSP extension, Pleasant Prairie, WI,1997 (Box 344, Folder 4)
  - NLB Harbor Improvements Oconto Co, WI,1997 (Box 344, Folder 5)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Big Rock Nuclear Plant, Charlevoix, 1 of 2,1997 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Big Rock Nuclear Plant, Charlevoix, 2 of 2,1997 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Big Rock Nuclear Plant, Charlevoix, Drawings, 1 of 3,1997 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Big Rock Nuclear Plant, Charlevoix, Drawings, 2 of 3,1997 (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - NLB Consumers Power, Big Rock Nuclear Plant, Charlevoix, Drawings, 3 of 3,1997 (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - NLB Rouge River Bridge Repair, Detroit,1997 (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - NLB Rouge River Bridge Repair, Detroit, Drawings,1997 (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - NLB Ludington Harbor Development Project, Ludington,1998 (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - NLB Ludington Harbor Development Project, Ludington, Proposal/ Plan,1998 (Box 345, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Repairs, White Lake, Construction Specs,1998 (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Repairs, White Lake,1998 (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Pier Repairs, Sault Ste. Marie,1998 (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - NLB Forebay and Screenwell Dredging, Dunkirk, NY,1998 (Box 346, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Repairs, Charlevoix, 1 of 2,1998 (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Repairs, Charlevoix, 2 of 2,1998 (Box 346, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East Pier Repairs, Cedar River,1998 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East Pier Repairs, Cedar River, Construction Specs,1998 (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East Pier Repairs, Cedar River, Blue-lines,1998 (Box 347, Folder 3)
  - NLB Ferry Office and Dock, Erie, PA,1998 (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - NLB 90-inch Outfall Sewers, Erie, PA,1998 (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - NLB Cherry Farm Sediment Removal, Tonawanda, NY,1998 (Box 347, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Buffalo, NY,1998 (Box 347, Folder 7)
  - NLB CRA Services, Wyandotte,1998 (Box 347, Folder 8)
  - NLB City of Menominee, Menominee, 1 of 2,1998 (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - NLB City of Menominee, Menominee, 2 of 2,1998 (Box 348, Folder 12)
  - NLB City of Menominee, Menominee, Blue-lines,1998 (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Detroit,1998 (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - NLB Detroit and Canada Tunnel Corp, Detroit, 1 of 2,1998 (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - NLB Detroit and Canada Tunnel Corp, Detroit, 2 of 2,1998 (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - NLB Detroit and Canada Tunnel Corp, Detroit, Drawings, 1 of 2,1998 (Box 348, Folder 7)
  - NLB Detroit and Canada Tunnel Corp, Detroit, Drawings, 2 of 2,1998 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie,1998 (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Contract,1998 (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines, 1 of 4,1998 (Box 349, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines, 2 of 4,1998 (Box 349, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines, 3 of 4,1998 (Box 349, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines, 4 of 4,1998 (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - NLB St Clair County, Algonac, 1 of 3,1998 (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - NLB St Clair County, Algonac, 2 of 3,1998 (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - NLB St Clair County, Algonac, 3 of 3,1998 (Box 350, Folder 4)
  - NLB City of Chicago, Chicago, IL,1998 (Box 350, Folder 5)
  - NLB Ohio Valley Electric Corporation, Cheshire, OH,1997 (Box 350, Folder 6)
  - NLB McConnell and Scully Inc., Manistee Lake,1998 (Box 350, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Mt. Morris, NY,1998 (Box 350, Folder 8)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie,1998 (Box 351, Folder 1)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): NLB Cedar Point, Sandusky, OH,1998 (Box 351, Folder 2)
  - (.25 cubic ft.): NLB LaFarge Corporation, Green Bay, WI,1998 (Box 351, Folder 3)
  - NLB City of Detroit, Detroit,1998 (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Bulkhead Repair, Marblehead, OH,1999 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Lighthouse Repair, Harbor Beach,1999 (Box 352, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Lighthouse Repair, Harbor Beach, Drawings,1999 (Box 352, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Shoreline Stabilization, Grand Haven,1999 (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Shoreline Stabilization, Grand Haven, Blue-lines,1999 (Box 352, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Haulout, Mooring, and Pier Work, Duluth, MN,1999 (Box 352, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Waterfront Renovations, St. Ignace,1999 (Box 352, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Waterfront Renovations, St. Ignace, Drawings,1999 (Box 353, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Pier Repairs, Saugatuck, 1 of 3,1999 (Box 353, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Pier Repairs, Saugatuck, Drawings and Photographs, 2 of 3,1999 (Box 353, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Pier Repairs, Saugatuck, Drawings, 3 of 3,1999 (Box 353, Folder 4)
  - NLB Wolverine Power, Repair Power Cable, Cross Village,1999 (Box 353, Folder 5)
  - NLB Intake Inspections, Wyoming and Muskegon,1999 (Box 353, Folder 6)
  - NLB Channel Dredging, Caseville,1999 (Box 353, Folder 7)
  - NLB Environmental River Dredging, Green Bay, WI,1999 (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - NLB Dock 22 East Slip Improvment, Cleveland, OH,1999 (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Repair of Dock and West Pier, Cleveland, OH,1999 (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Mechanical Dredging, Rock Island, IL,1999 (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - NLB Bridge Fender Repair, Toledo, OH,1999 (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - NLB Bridge Fender Repair, Cleveland, OH,1999 (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East Pier Repairs, Ontognagon Harbor,1999 (Box 354, Folder 7)
  - NLB CSX Transportation Bridge 44, Ferrysburg,1999 (Box 354, Folder 8)
  - NLB Repairs to North Piers and Revetments, Pentwater Harbor,1999 (Box 354, Folder 9)
  - NLB Repairs to North Piers and Revetments, Pentwater Harbor, Drawings,1999 (Box 354, Folder 10)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Stone Supply, Buffalo, NY,1999 (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - NLB Water Systems Improvements, Village of Lexington,1999 (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - NLB Dam Modifications, Edenville,1999 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Chicago Shoreline Storm Drain Reduction, Chicago, IL, Reach #2,1999 (Box 355, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East and West Breakwater Repairs, Manistique Harbor,1999 (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East and West Breakwater Repairs, Manistique Harbor,, Drawings,1999 (Box 355, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East-West Breakwater Repairs, Manistique Harbor, Drawings and Photographs,1999 (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - NLB Phase #1 Sediment Remedial Action, St. Louis,1999 (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - NLB Launching Ramp, St. Ignace,1999 (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Stone Revetment Along Lake Michigan, Escanaba,1999 (Box 356, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Phase 2 Repairs to MacArthur Lock, Sault Ste. Marie,1999 (Box 356, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Phase 2 Repairs to MacArthur Lock, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings,1999 (Box 356, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Phase 2 Repairs to MacArthur Lock, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings and Photographs,1999 (Box 356, Folder 7)
  - NLB Village Dock Reconstruction, Egg Harbor, WI,1999 (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Install Camels and Rub Rails, Cleveland, OH,1999 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - NLB Renovation and Expansion of Town Marina, Baily’s Harbor, WI,1999 (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Navigation Tower, Northport,1999 (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Inflatable Dam, Flint,1999 (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Inflatable Dam, Flint, Blue-lines and Drawings,1999 (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - NLB Bridge Replacement, Kaleva,1999 (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - NLB Bridge Street Boat Launch, Elk Rapids,1999 (Box 357, Folder 8)
  - NLB Bridge Street Boat Launch, Elk Rapids, Drawings and Photographs,1999 (Box 357, Folder 9)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Taconite Harbor of Refuge, Taconite Harbor, MN,1999 (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - NLB Place Armor Stone Over Bedding Stone, Sodus Point NY,1999 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - NLB Linnie Lac Dredging, New Berlin, WI,1999 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Lock Repair, Menasha, WI,1999 (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - NLB 42-inch Water Intake, Muskegon Heights,1999 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - NLB Marina Dredging, Village of Suttons Bay,2000 (Box 358, Folder 6)
  - NLB Dam Demolition and Sediment Removal, Big Rapids,2000 (Box 358, Folder 7)
  - NLB Dam Demolition and Sediment Removal, Big Rapids, Drawings and Photographs,2000 (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Submarine Cable Work, Great Lakes Area,2000 (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - NLB Harbor Dredging and Improvements, Grosse Pointe,2000 (Box 359, Folder 3)
  - NLB Emergency Dredging of Bois Blanc Island Pier, Pointe Aux Pins,2000 (Box 359, Folder 4)
  - NLB Submarine Cables, St. Joe,2000 (Box 359, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Repairs to Guide Walls, St. Mary’s River,2000 (Box 359, Folder 6)
  - NLB Marina – Inner Harbor Wall Improvements, Grosse Pointe,2000 (Box 359, Folder 7)
  - NLB Breakwater Extension and Fishing Platform, Rogers City,2000 (Box 359, Folder 8)
  - NLB Breakwater Extension and Fishing Platform, Rogers City, Drawings,2000 (Box 360, Folder 1)
  - NLB Breakwater Extension and Fishing Platform, Rogers City, Drawings and Photographs,2000 (Box 360, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Dredging, St. Clair Shores,2000 (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - NLB Dredging, City of Grosse Pointe Woods,2000 (Box 360, Folder 4)
  - NLB CSX Transportation, Toledo, OH,2000 (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - NLB LaFarge Corporation, Alpena,2000 (Box 360, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Alpena Harbor,2000 (Box 360, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Alpena Harbor, Drawings,2000 (Box 360, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Lake County, OH,2000 (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cleveland, OH,2000 (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - NLB Gateway Trade Center, Buffalo, NY,2000 (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Porter County, IN,2000 (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - NLB Detroit Edison Company, Harbor Beach,2000 (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Rocky River, OH,2000 (Box 361, Folder 6)
  - NLB Eastern U.P. Transportation Authority, Drummond Island,2000 (Box 361, Folder 7)
  - NLB Eastern U.P. Transportation Authority, Drummond Island, Drawings,2000 (Box 361, Folder 8)
  - NLB LaFarge Corporation, Carrollton,2000 (Box 361, Folder 9)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Cleveland, OH,2000 (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Lorain, OH,2000 (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - NLB Norfolk Southern Railway, Bridge Rehabilitation, Rouge River,2000 (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - NLB Bay Aggregate Relocation Site, Contract #1 – Sheet Piling, Bay City,2000 (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - NLB Bay Aggregate Relocation Site, Contract #1 – Sheet Piling, Bay City, Drawings,2000 (Box 362, Folder 5)
  - NLB Bay Aggregate Relocation Site, Contract #2 – Slip Dredging, Bay City,2000 (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - NLB Bay Aggregate Relocation Site, Contract #2 – Slip Dredging, Bay City, Drawings,2000 (Box 362, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Repair, Cook County, IL,2000 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - NLB Outfall Rehabilitation, St. Clair Shores,2000 (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - NLB Outfall Rehabilitation, St. Clair Shores, Drawings and Photographs,2000 (Box 363, Folder 3)
  - NLB Rubblemound Breakwater, Sandusky, OH,2000 (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - NLB Net Repair and Installation, Ludington,2000 (Box 363, Folder 5)
  - NLB MDOT, Structural and Fender Repair, Wayne City,2000 (Box 363, Folder 6)
  - NLB MDOT, Structural and Fender Repair, Wayne City, Drawings,2000 (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - NLB Rubblemound and Dredging, Door County, WI,2000 (Box 363, Folder 8)
  - NLB Breakwater Rehabilitation, Cleveland, OH,2000 (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - NLB Breakwater Rehabilitation, Cleveland, OH, Contract,2000 (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Upgrade Boat Haulout, U.S. Coast Guard Base Detroit,2000 (Box 364, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Reroof Three light Lighthouse, Straits of Mackinac,2000 (Box 364, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Reroof Three light Lighthouse, Straits of Mackinac, Drawings and Photographs,2000 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Reroof Three light Lighthouse, Straits of Mackinac, Drawings and Photographs,2000 (Box 364, Folder 6)
  - NLB Runway Paving, South Fox Island,2000 (Box 364, Folder 7)
  - NLB Ottawa County, MI, Lake Michigan, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - NLB Ottawa County, MI, Lake Michigan, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - NLB Ottawa County, MI, Lake Michigan, Drawings,2001 (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Grand Haven,2001 (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Grand Haven, Drawings,2001 (Box 365, Folder 5)
  - NLB NY Department of Environmental Conservation, Strawberry Island, NY,2001 (Box 365, Folder 6)
  - NLB Covert Generating Company, South Haven, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 365, Folder 7)
  - NLB Covert Generating Company, South Haven, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 365, Folder 8)
  - NLB Covert Generating Company, South Haven, Drawings,2001 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - NLB LaFarge Corporation, Detroit,2001 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - NLB Toledo Edison Company, Oak Harbor, OH,2001 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - NLB City of Petoskey, Petoskey,2001 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - NLB City of Munising, Munising,2001 (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cedar River, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 366, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cedar River, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cedar River, Drawings,2001 (Box 366, Folder 8)
  - NLB Nuclear Management Company, Point Beach, WI,2001 (Box 366, Folder 9)
  - NLB City of Sault Ste. Marie, Sault Ste. Marie,2001 (Box 367, Folder 1)
  - NLB City of Sault Ste. Marie, Sault Ste. Marie, Blue-lines,2001 (Box 367, Folder 2)
  - NLB City of Munising, Munising,2001 (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings, 1 of 3,2001 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings, 2 of 3,2001 (Box 367, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings, 3 of 3,2001 (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace, Blue-lines, 1 of 2,2001 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace, Blue-lines, 2 of 2,2001 (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - NLB MI Department of Natural Resources, Mackinac Island,2001 (Box 368, Folder 6)
  - NLB MI Department of Natural Resources, Mackinac Island, Photographs,2001 (Box 369, Folder 1)
  - NLB City of Escanaba, Escanaba,2001 (Box 369, Folder 2)
  - NLB City of Escanaba, Escanaba, Drawings,2001 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - NLB LaFarge Corporation, Waukegan, IL,2001 (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Grand River, OH,2001 (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - NLB LaFarge Corporation, St. Joseph,2001 (Box 369, Folder 6)
  - NLB MI Department of Natural Resources, Au Gres,2001 (Box 369, Folder 7)
  - NLB Maria Dredging, City of Escanaba,2001 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Waterfront Rebuild Station, Port Huron,2001 (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Waterfront Rebuild Station, Port Huron, Drawings,2001 (Box 370, Folder 3)
  - NLB Marina Renovations – Phase II, Elk Rapids,2001 (Box 370, Folder 4)
  - NLB Marina Renovations – Phase II, Elk Rapids, Drawings,2001 (Box 370, Folder 5)
  - NLB Detroit Water Sewerage District, 48-inch Discharge Line, Port Huron,2001 (Box 370, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Sault Ste. Marie,2001 (Box 370, Folder 7)
  - NLB Dredging and Clean Up, White Lake,2001 (Box 370, Folder 8)
  - NLB Dredging, Manitowoc, WI,2001 (Box 370, Folder 9)
  - NLB Dredging, Manitowoc, WI,2001 (Box 370, Folder 10)
  - NLB Steel Sheet Pile Bulkhead, Manistee,2001 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - NLB Water Main / Sewer Outfall, Bay City,2001 (Box 371, Folder 2)
  - NLB Water Intake Upgrade, Burns Harbor, IN,2001 (Box 371, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, North Revetment Repairs, South Haven,2002 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, North Revetment Repairs, South Haven, Drawings,2002 (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, Dredging Boat Basin, St. Ignace,2002 (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East and West Pier Repairs, Ontonagon,2002 (Box 371, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East and West Pier Repairs, Ontonagon, Drawings,2002 (Box 372, Folder 1)
  - NLB Clinch Park Marina Improvements, Traverse City,2002 (Box 372, Folder 2)
  - NLB Clinch Park Marina Improvements, Traverse City, Drawings, 1 of 3,2002 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - NLB Clinch Park Marina Improvements, Traverse City, Drawings, 2 of 3,2002 (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - NLB Clinch Park Marina Improvements, Traverse City, Drawings, 3 of 3,2002 (Box 372, Folder 5)
  - NLB Environmental Dredging, White Lake,2002 (Box 372, Folder 6)
  - NLB Environmental Dredging, White Lake, Drawings,2002 (Box 372, Folder 7)
  - NLB Launching Ramp Construction and Dredging, Bois Blanc,2002 (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Stone Supply, Hancock,2002 (Box 373, Folder 2)
  - NLB Edison Sault Electric Company, Sault Ste. Marie,2002 (Box 373, Folder 3)
  - NLB South Breakwater Rehabilitation, Racine Harbor, WI,2002 (Box 373, Folder 4)
  - NLB Root River Dredging, Racine, WI,2002 (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie,2002 (Box 373, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings, 1 of 2,2002 (Box 373, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings, 2 of 2,2002 (Box 373, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Two Rivers Harbor, WI,2002 (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Two Rivers Harbor, WI, Drawings,2002 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace,2002 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - NLB City of St. Ignace, St. Ignace, Blue Line Drawings,2002 (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - NLB Lorain Sailing and Yacht Club, Lorain, OH,2002 (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - NLB NE Ohio Regional Sewer District, Cleveland, OH,2002 (Box 375, Folder 2)
  - NLB Environmental Engineering U.S. Steel, Gary, IN,2002 (Box 375, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, St. Clair Shores,2002 (Box 375, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, St. Clair Shores, Drawings, 1 of 2,2002 (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Coast Guard, St. Clair Shores, Drawings, 2 of 2,2002 (Box 375, Folder 6)